So, we're going to take our arm balance where the knees are over the shoulders -- Lazy Tortoise, Lazy Firefly and then Straight Leg Firefly.
So, in order to help get the knees really over the backs of the shoulders in a powerful way, we do Standing Firefly.
In Standing Firefly, we come forward.
This little series of poses, well, it gets you in touch with the absurdity of poses in general, funny little shapes that we make.
But, we pull through and you can get that strap.
That's why it's there.
That's why I've got a strap around my waist.
And pull through and get the strap.
And then you can get your shoulders a little further back and just pull yourself through a little bit.
Of course, if you don't need the strap, you can just hold your hands together.
That's even better, but I may have to wait for another lifetime for that one.
I'm not sure.
So then, look how I'm getting my feet right on top of my hands.
I'm going to sit back.
At first, I'm going to do a Lazy Firefly, which I have to say I really prefer because it's a little lazy.
Bend the legs.
Pull with the feet.
Then, big firefly, straighten the legs.
Then, we get to take a little rest and sit down.
And the arms are really deep underneath legs, so it's very convenient, this transition into a nice Tortoise.
Well, you push down with the legs, elongate the legs.
Reach out to the arms, the spine, everything.
And yet, you can also take a little nap and be Sleeping Tortoise.